

CONTACT

- +48 889 487 298
- Płock, Poland
- krywa5
- in krystianwasilewski

EDUCATION

2019 CODERS LAB

 Classroom course "JavaScript developer: React" (320h)

2013 - 2018 WARSAW UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

- Course: Construction engineering
- Degree: Engineer

SKILLS

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Adaptability
- Creativity
- Empathy
- Critical thinking
- Continuous learning
- Attention to detail

LANGUAGUES

- English (fluent)
- B2 exam
- Working with a foreign client
- Working in England five times during the vacations

KRYSTIAN WASILEWSKI

SENIOR FRONTEND/REACT DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Krystian and since 2019 I have been professionally developing web applications. My analytical approach and passion for new technologies translate into successful implementations of innovative solutions that meet and exceed client expectations. I am convinced that the key to success is transforming complex requirements into a simple, elegant form that brings value to both users and business. I am enthusiastic and eager to support the implementation of projects that will benefit and satisfy both you and the users of your applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fabrity Sp. z o.o.

Senior React developer

05.2023 - PRESENT

- Develop and improve a web applications to manage transportation organization for an international agency.
- Communication with foreign customer.
- **Tech stack**: React, TypeScript, Redux, Fluent UI, module SCSS, Enzyme, SharePoint, TanStack Query.

Bytespack sp. z o.o.

02.2021 - 04.2023

React developer

- Creating from the scratch a web application for cost estimating and calculating the carbon footprint of construction projects based on BIM methodology.
- Tech stack: React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, Material UI, DevExtreme, SCSS. Styled Components, React Testing Library, Tanstack Query, Storybook.

Lion Head Studio

07.2019 - 01.2021

Frontend developer

- Creating responsive websites based on Wordpress, Vue and React. Building applications from scratch and maintaining existing ones.
- Tech stack: React, Vue, JavaScript, PHP, WordPress, LESS/SCSS



CONTACT

- +48 889 487 298
- Płock, Poland
- krywa5
- in krystianwasilewski

KRYSTIAN WASILEWSKI

SENIOR FRONTEND/REACT DEVELOPER

TECHNOLOGIES

- React (15-19)
- Vue
- Next.js
- TypeScript
- JavaScript (ES6)
- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- PHP 7
- WordPress
- Node.js
- Express
- Mongo DB
- Unit tests (Jest, RTL, Enzyme)
- End-to-End tests (Cypress)

- Google Firebase API
- Material UI
- Fluent UI
- DevExtreme
- Bootstrap
- Styled Components
- Redux Toolkit
- Tanstack Query
- Axios
- Formik
- Storybook
- BEM
- jQuery
- GIT

TOOLS

- Jira
- Azure DevOps
- Asana
- Trello
- Figma

- BitBucket
- GitHub
- Teams
- Zoom
- Slack

PRIVATE PROJECTS

- <u>Tax Tool</u> A tool for calculating taxes in Poland from foreign incomes.
 React, TypeScript, Material UI, Firebase, Styled Components, Toastify, NBP API.
- <u>Income Manager</u> A tool to convert foreign revenues into Polish zloty.
 React, TypeScript, Material UI, Styled Components.
- Forkify Recipes search engine. HTML, CSS, Forkify API, Local Storage.
- <u>Burger Builder</u> An app for creating custom burgers. React, *HTML*, *CSS Modules*, *Firebase*.
- <u>Portfolio</u> My portfolio as a Server-Side-Rendering application.
 Next.js, React, TypeScript, Tailwind.

HOBBIES

New technologies, non-fiction, puzzles, football (Spanish league, English league and international football), running, series and films (documentaries, action, thrillers).

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.